(Penny:)Awkward silence.
Sheldon on his phone.
(Penny:)No touching.
Somebody's having date night.
(Amy:)It's actually steamier than it looks.
(Amy:)Sheldon's looking up the phallic
symbolism of root vegetables
(Amy:)in Renaissance paintings.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no,
I got bored with that.
(Sheldon:)I'm just browsing cuticle scissors
on Amazon.
(Penny:)How do you not tear off his clothes
and take him here on this table?
(Sheldon:)If you do that, I'll scream.
(Amy:)Sheldon, I have some exciting news
to tell you.
(Sheldon:)That makes two of us.
My new cuticle scissors will be here
(Sheldon:)in one to two business days.
(Sheldon:)Come on, one.
(Amy:)I've been invited to consult
on an experiment
(Amy:)at your university for a few months.
(Amy:)Isn't that great?
We could have lunch together.
(Amy:)We could carpool.
(Sheldon:)You know, riding with Leonard
has gotten a little tedious lately.
(Sheldon:)The only car game he ever wants
to play is the Quiet Game.